SEARCH

1. [Home](https://www.addictivetips.com/ "Home")

Privacy Policy
==============

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of AddictiveTips.

AddictiveTips will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on AddictiveTips.

AddictiveTips uses Google Adsense to display advertisement and Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to AddictiveTips users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

AddictiveTips is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows AddictiveTips to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and AddictiveTips does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to AddictiveTips and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through AddictiveTips have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information, please use the contact form [here](https://www.addictivetips.com/contact/).

### Mediavine Programmatic Advertising (Ver 1.1)

The Website works with Mediavine to manage third-party interest-based advertising appearing on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use first and third-party cookies. A cookie is a small text file which is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so that a website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website.

First party cookies are created by the website that you are visiting. A third-party cookie is frequently used in behavioral advertising and analytics and is created by a domain other than the website you are visiting. Third-party cookies, tags, pixels, beacons and other similar technologies (collectively, “Tags”) may be placed on the Website to monitor interaction with advertising content and to target and optimize advertising. Each internet browser has functionality so that you can block both first and third-party cookies and clear your browser’s cache. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, how to disable existing cookies and how to clear your browser’s cache. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [All About Cookies](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

Without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website content and features. Please note that rejecting cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site. In the event you opt-out, you will still see non-personalized advertisements on the Website.

The Website collects the following data using a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP Address
* Operating System type
* Operating System version
* Device Type
* Language of the website
* Web browser type
* Email (in hashed form)

Mediavine Partners (companies listed below with whom Mediavine shares data) may also use this data to link to other end user information the partner has independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements. Mediavine Partners may also separately collect data about end users from other sources, such as advertising IDs or pixels, and link that data to data collected from Mediavine publishers in order to provide interest-based advertising across your online experience, including devices, browsers and apps. This data includes usage data, cookie information, device information, information about interactions between users and advertisements and websites, geolocation data, traffic data, and information about a visitor’s referral source to a particular website. Mediavine Partners may also create unique IDs to create audience segments, which are used to provide targeted advertising.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [National Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://thenai.org/opt-out/). You may also visit [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/) and [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#) to learn more information about interest-based advertising. You may download the AppChoices app at [Digital Advertising Alliance’s AppChoices app](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out in connection with mobile apps, or use the platform controls on your mobile device to opt out.

For specific information about Mediavine Partners, the data each collects and their data collection and privacy policies, please visit [Mediavine Partners](https://www.mediavine.com/ad-partners/).

Mediavine partners with the following data processors:

1. Pubmatic. You may find Pubmatic’s privacy policy [through this link](https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/). The data collected on the Website may be transferred to Pubmatic and its demand partners for interest-based advertising. Statistical information and other non-cookie technologies (such as eTags and web or browser cache) may be used by third parties on this Website. Browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on these technologies, but you may clear your cache to delete such trackers. Data collected from a particular browser or device may be used with another computer or device that is linked to the browser or device on which such data was collected.
2. Criteo. You may find Criteo’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/). The data collected on the Website may be transferred to Criteo and its demand partners for interest-based advertising. Criteo may collect, access, and use non-identifying data to improve the Criteo Technology and other Criteo products, programs, and/or services. This non-identifying data may include on-site user behavior and user/page content data, URLs, statistics, or internal search queries. The non-identifying data are collected through the ad call and stored with a Criteo cookie for a maximum period of 13 months.
3. Pulsepoint. You may find Pulsepoint’s privacy policy [through this link](https://pulsepoint.com/legal/platform-privacy-policy).
4. LiveRamp. You may find LiveRamp’s privacy policy [through this link](https://liveramp.com/privacy/). When you use the Website, we share information that we may collect from you, such as your email (in hashed, de-identified form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with LiveRamp Inc, and its group companies (‘LiveRamp’). LiveRamp may use a cookie on your browser and match your shared information to their on- and offline marketing databases and those of its advertising partners to create a link between your browser and information in those other databases. This link may be shared by our partners globally for the purpose of enabling interest-based content or advertising throughout your online experience (e.g. cross device, web, email, in-app, etc.) by third parties unaffiliated with our website. These third parties may in turn link further demographic or interest-based information to your browser. To opt out of LiveRamp’s targeted advertising, please go here: [https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)
5. RhythmOne. You may view RhythmOne’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy). RhythmOne uses cookies and similar tracking technologies (such as mobile device identifiers and digital fingerprinting) to provide its services. RhythmOne may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the following webpage: [https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
6. District M. You may find District M’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.districtm.net/platforms-data-privacy-policy/).
7. YieldMo. You may find YieldMo’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.yieldmo.com/privacy-policy/). If you want to opt out of receiving interest based ads from Yieldmo or exercise your right under the [California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)](https://www.oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa) to opt-out of the sale of your personal information, you may do so [through this link](https://www.yieldmo.com/opt-out/).
8. The Rubicon Project. You may find Rubicon’s privacy policy [through this link](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/). If you want to opt out of receiving interest based ads from Rubicon or exercise your right under the [California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)](https://www.oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa) to opt-out of the sale of your personal information, you may do so [through this link](https://www.rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/). You may also utilize the [Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/), the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youradchoices.com/), or the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).
9. Amazon Publisher Services. You may find Amazon Publisher Services’ privacy policy [through this link](https://aps.amazon.com/aps/privacy-policy/).
10. AppNexus. You may find the AppNexus privacy policy [through this link](https://www.appnexus.com/platform-privacy-policy-072016).
11. OpenX. You may find OpenX’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/).
12. Verizon Media formerly known as Oath. You may find Verizon Media’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.verizonmedia.com/policies/us/en/verizonmedia/privacy/index.html). You may also utilize the [Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/), the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youradchoices.com/), or the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) to opt-out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising.
13. TripleLift. You may find TripleLift’s privacy policy [through this link](https://triplelift.com/privacy/). To opt out of receiving interest-based advertising (including retargeting) from TripleLift’s services through the use of cookies in your current browser and for more information on what it means to opt-out, please go to [www.triplelift.com/consumer-opt-out](https://triplelift.com/consumer-opt-out/).
14. Index Exchange. You may find Index Exchange’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/). You may also utilize the [Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/), the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youradchoices.com/), or the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) to opt-out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising.
15. Sovrn. You may find Sovrn’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/).
16. GumGum. You may find GumGum’s privacy policy [through this link](https://gumgum.com/privacy-policy). GumGum may (i) use place and use cookies on end users’ browsers or use web beacons to collect information about end users who visit such Publisher Websites and (ii) link such collected end user information to other end user information provided by third parties in order to deliver targeted Advertisements to such end users.
17. Digital Remedy. You may find Digital Remedy’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.digitalremedy.com/privacy-policy/).
18. MediaGrid. You may find MediaGrid’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.themediagrid.com/privacy-policy/). MediaGrid may collect and store information about end-user interactions with this website through cookies, advertising IDS, pixels and server-to-server connections. MediaGrid was receive the following information: the page an End-User has requested and the referring/exit pages; Timestamp information (i.e., the date and time the End-User has visited the page); IP address; mobile device identifier; device model; device operating system; browser type; carrier; gender; age; geolocation (including GPS coordinates); clickstream data; cookie information; first-party identifiers’; and hashed email addresses; demographic and inferred interest information; and post-conversion data (from both online and offline behaviour). Some of this data is gathered from this website and others is gathered from advertisers. MediaGrid uses this data to provide its services. You may also utilize the [Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/), the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youradchoices.com/), or the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) to opt-out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising or review their privacy policy for more information.
19. RevContent – You may find RevContent’s privacy policy [through this link](https://intercom.help/revcontent2/en/articles/2290675-revcontent-s-privacy-policy). RevContent may collect information about your browser or device, including browser type, IP Address, device type, user agent string, and operating system. RevContent also collects information about the websites you visit through their services, such as date and time of access and specific pages accessed and the content and ads you click on. You may opt-out of any personalization track by [opting-out of RevContent’s data collection](https://www.revcontent.com/legal/optout/).
20. Centro, Inc. – You may find Centro’s privacy policy [through this link](https://privacy.centro.net/). You may find opt-out information for Centro’s services through the privacy policy link.
21. 33Across, Inc. – You may find 33Across’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.33across.com/privacy-policy/). To opt-out of personalized advertising, please visit [https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).
22. Conversant. LLC – You may find Conversant’s privacy policy [through this link](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy). Conversant uses information that does not directly identify you, such as information about your browser type, time and date of visit, your browsing or transaction activity, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, and a unique identifier (such as a cookie string, or a unique advertising identifier provided by your mobile device) during your visits to this and other websites and apps in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. Conversant may use technologies such as cookies and other tracking technologies to collect this information. To learn more about interest-based advertising, or to opt-out, you can visit [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) or [https://www.networkadvertising.org/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### 2 Comments

1. 

    **Lily Allen** says:

    Hi,  
    I just visit your website and just notice that you are providing guest posts on your website.  
    Let me know if you are interested in the offer and share your best prices as well.  
    Kind regards

2. 

    **Vanessa Seward** says:

    Hello addictivetips.com,
    
    My name is Vanessa Seward, I’m an outreach manager at Strictly Digital. I’m passionate about exploring and writing about innovation, technology including VPN, Streaming, and Netflix marketing trends. I also manage my personal blog where I actively share my thoughts on Streaming, Security and trending technologies.
    
    The reason I’m reaching out is to ask if you are accepting the sponsored post. I understand the need for unique and well-researched content, and I am also very passionate about any topic or subject that I write about. Is it still room for me to write some actionable and useful content on your blog???
    
    In particular, we’re interested in site owners who can provide the content written by their staff, with a do-follow backlink.
    
    Awaiting your positive reply,
    
    Best regards,
    
    Vanessa E. Seward,  
    Outreach manager  
    Strictly Digital

### Leave a Reply [Cancel reply](https://www.addictivetips.com/privacy-policy/#respond)

You must be [logged in](https://www.addictivetips.com/wp/wp-login.php?redirect_to=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.addictivetips.com%2Fprivacy-policy%2F) to post a comment.

This site uses Akismet to reduce spam. [Learn how your comment data is processed](https://akismet.com/privacy/).

Searching for something else?
-----------------------------

Chances are, we can find what you're looking for:

 SEARCH
